ALI AMINI

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- Aliaminii1422@gmail.com 09142566457
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ lali-amini-25b53524a
- https://github.com/aliaminil ()

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science Software Engineering University of Bonab 2017-2021

SKILLS

PHP, Laravel
JavaScript, TypeScript, React
Adonis.js
Redux, RTK Query
API Development
MySQL, MongoDB
Ionic
Figma
HTML, CSS, Tailwind
Redis
Git

SUMMARY

I am a full stack developer with more than 2 years of experience. proficient in crafting responsive websites and highly performant RESTful APIs using PHP, Laravel, and JavaScript frameworks like React. Demonstrated ability in Git version control and team collaboration.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Vista

2023 - 2024

- Managed source control repositories with Git, including branching strategies and pull requests.
- Developed responsive websites based on client requirements.
- Created RESTful APIs using Node.js with Adonis.js framework for data manipulation.
- Work with cross-functional teams to identify and resolve technical issues
- Worked with team of developers to add features, fix bugs, and make upgrades to existing applications.

Full Stack Developer

Tutianet

2022 - 2023

- Implemented Git version control and collaborated with development teams
- Develop and maintain Front-end applications using React, Next, Ionic, Alpine JS HTML, CSS, JS and Tailwind.
- Develop and maintain Back-end applications using PHP, Laravel and MySQL.
- Created reusable components that can be shared across different projects, reducing development time.
- Built highly performant RESTful APIs leveraging caching techniques such as Redis and using RTK Query.